Guide to the United Mission to Nepal Records
Yale University Divinity School Library
- J, Series X
  - Jumala Project and KCST
    - Maps
      - Including Jumala project plans: J-01.03.01, 1981, n.d. (Box 87, Folder 8)
    - Correspondence
      - Correspondence, etc.: J-01.04.01/0001-J-01.04.01/0015 - RESTRICTED, 1979- 1986 (Box 88, Folder 1-4)
      - Correspondence, etc.: J-01.04.02/0001- J-01.04.02/0021 - RESTRICTED, 1986-1996 (Box 88, Folder 5-7)
    - Building
      - Reports; Minutes; Correspondence, etc: J-01.05.01, 1978-1990 (Box 87, Folder 5-6)
  - Japan Overseas Christian Medical Cooperative Service
    - Correspondence: J-02.00.01 (Box 89, Folder 3)
  - Japan Antioch Mission
    - Correspondence: J-03.00.01, 1993 May- 1999 Aug (Box 89, Folder 2)
  - Jajarkot Project
    - Reports: J-04.01.01/0001- J-04.01.01/0019, 1985 Mar- 1991 May (Box 89, Folder 6)
      Including regarding: Report on visit to Jajarkot; Peace Corps work in Jajarkot; Planning meeting by 3 Functional Secretaries; Report on education visit; Concept paper; UNICEF grant for literacy materials
    - Reports: J-04.01.01/0020- J-04.01.01/0039, 1991- 1992 Sep (Box 89, Folder 7)
      Including regarding: Opening ceremony of UMN project; Annual report and statement; PMC minutes; Plans for freight transport; PMC meeting; Evaluation of Jagtipur adult participants
    - Reports: J-04.01.01/0040- J-04.01.01/0049, 1992- 1993 Sep (Box 89, Folder 8)
      Including regarding: Sample employment contract; Development activities in Jajarkot; PMC minutes; Regarding application of NFE; Political problems; Discussion on action regarding political problems
    - Reports: J-04.01.01/0050- J-04.01.01/0055, 1993 Oct- 1994 Jun (Box 89, Folder 9)
      Including regarding: Letter with description of project; Long-term plan 1994-1999; PMC minutes; Health aspects of NFE; A visit with Rhonda Yodes; Report from Kath Bosscher; District profile, Jajarkot
    - Reports: J-04.01.01/0056- J-04.01.01/0061, 1994 Jul- Sep (Box 89, Folder 10)
      Including regarding: Project description; Annual reports; PMC minutes; Copy of Agreement Phase II; Facilitator Training Reports, 10 and 12 September
    - Reports: J-04.01.02/0001- J-04.01.02/0007, 1995 Jan- 1995 Aug (Box 90, Folder 1)
      Including regarding: Annual plan 1995/96; PMC minutes; Reports on Women's work; Skills for survival; Report on training program (Nepali); Silk screen printing
    - Reports: J-04.01.02/0008 - J -04.01.02/0017, 1995 Nov- 1997 Feb (Box 90, Folder 2)
      Including regarding: Detailed and Summary Annual Plan 1996/97; Definition of women's awareness; PMC minutes; Funding application; Map of district; Report of Community based disaster training with full details
    - Report of Community-Based Disaster training: J-04.01.02/0016, 1997 (Box 161, Folder 4)
    - Reports: J-04.01.02/0018- J-04.01.02/0031, 1997 Feb- 1998 Mar (Box 90, Folder 3)
      Including regarding: PMC minutes; Community Reading Centre: a brief report; Proposal for Jajarkot; Staff Association requests and response; NFE and TOT seminars
    - Reports: J-04.01.02/0032- J-04.01.02/0057, 1998 Mar- 2000 Jan (Box 90, Folder 4)
      Including regarding: Report of HIV/AIDS visit; Suspension of program; Meeting with senior staff; Summary and Detailed Annual Reports; PMC minutes; Data gathering guideline; Project Activities Review Program
    - Reports: J-04.01.03/0050- J-04.01.03/0057 (Box 90, Folder 5)
      Including regarding: NFE Project
    - Reports, plans (closed 2001, Maoist threat): (J-04.01), 1993-2001 (Box 208, Folder 7)
    - Jajarkot NFE Project: photo album: (J-04.01) (Box 209, Folder 1)
    - Correspondence: J-04.02.01/0001- J-04.02.01/0009 - RESTRICTED, 1993-1999 (Box 89, Folder 2)
  - Jhimruk Project
    - Reports: J-05.01.01/0001- J-05.01.01/0019, 1987 Sep- 1989 Apr (Box 90, Folder 6)
      Including regarding: Notes of meeting; Jhimruk Project: A brief description; Development of hydropower related industry; UMN and Jhimruk: What is involved; Memo of Understanding: NHAM and UMN; Progress report
    - Reports: J-05.01.01/0020- J-05.01.01/0044, 1989 May- 1990 Jul (Box 90, Folder 7)
      Including regarding: Meetings on anthropology, finance, construction, housing; Draft concept paper; Progress Monitoring Committee (PMC) minutes; Progress reports; JHP and its impact on local people; Reports to Board on strike
    - Reports: J-05.01.01/0045- J-05.01.01/0074, 1990 Jul- 1992 Sep (Box 90, Folder 8)
      Including regarding: Accident report; Report on site closure; Bridge accident and death on site; PMC minutes; Progress reports; Draft proposal for rural development component
    - Reports: J-05.01.01/0075- J-05.01.01/0081, 1992 Oct- 1993 (Box 91, Folder 1)
      Including regarding: Progress reports; Report on work related injuries at Jhimruk; Jhimruk clinics; Write up on Jhimruk; Presentation on Jhimruk at UMN Board
    - Reports: J-05.01.01/0082- J-05.01.01/0091, 1994 Mar- 1995 Dec (Box 91, Folder 2)
      Including regarding: Residual flow; The price of power; The future status of JHEREP; Progress reports; Brief report on operations and project status; Handing over document of JHEREP
    - Reports: J-05.01.02/0001- J-05.01.02/0011, 1996 Jan- 1998 Apr (Box 91, Folder 3)
      Including regarding: Paper on JHEREP Phase II; Minutes of meeting with Jhimruk Centre; Report to EC; Agreement with BPC; FC-EC discussions; Incorporation of JIDCO
    - Reports: J-05.01.02/0012- J-05.01.02/0021, 1996 Jan- 1999 Jul (Box 91, Folder 4)
      Including regarding: Brochure; Update plans with historical background; Proposal for Baseline Survey and Need Assessment; Report on Nutrition visit; Agreement with BTI regarding Apprenticeship Training
    - Reports, plans, etc.: (J-05.01), 1997-2005 (Box 209, Folder 2-3)
    - Correspondence: J-05.02.01 - RESTRICTED, 1988 Jul- 1992 May (Box 89, Folder 4)
      Including regarding: Correspondence; Guesthouse meeting; GSO report; Report on Jhimruk TG
    - AGM minutes, meetings 1-9: (J-05.03), 1999-2007 (Box 209, Folder 4)
    - Board meeting minutes: (J-05.04), 1998-2008 (Box 210, Folder 1)
- K, Series XI
  - Kathmandu Housing and Area Committee
    - Kathmandu Area Committee Minutes of meetings 10 March 1959 - 19 July 1972; Shanta Bhawan Housing Committee: Minutes of meetings 31 August 1972- 10 October 1974: K-01.00.01/0001 - K-01.00.01/0002 - RESTRICTED, 1959-1974 (Box 91, Folder 5)
    - Kathmandu Valley Housing Committee records: K-01.00.01/0004 - K-01.00.01/0024 - RESTRICTED, 1969 -1996 (Box 91, Folder 6-8)
  - Korea Christian Medico-Evangelical Association
    - Correspondence (Box 92, Folder 2)
  - Khimti Project
    - Reports, etc - Nepal Electricity Authority :K-03.01.01/0001, 1987 (Box 164, Folder 4)
    - Reports, etc.: K-03.01.01/0002 - K-03.01.01/0009, 1991 Feb- Dec (Box 92, Folder 3)
      Including regarding: Update on a future hydropower project; Preliminary proposals for additional site investigation; Feasibility study briefing report; Brief account of present status
    - Reports, etc.: K-03.01.01/0010 - K-03.01.01/0024, 1992 Jan- 1993 Jan (Box 92, Folder 4)
      Including regarding: Initial project appraisal; Comments on finance and income; Present status; More than mere money; Letter regarding guarantees by HMG; Discussion with NCF report; Update on Himal Power
    - Reports, etc.: K-03.01.01/0025 - K-03.01.01/0038, 1993 Feb- 1994 Jun (Box 92, Folder 5)
      Including regarding: Comments regarding health issues, Jhimruk medical staff; Khimti hydropower health philosophy for Khimti; Administration organization chart; Hurdles in Khimti Project implementation; Report of EC actions
    - Reports, etc.: K-03.01.01/0039 - K-03.01.01/0051, 1994 Jul- 1996 Jun (Box 92, Folder 6)
      Including regarding: General Manager's Report to Board; Amendment to Agreement; Notice of closure; Memorandum of understanding; Updates; Clinical information; Extraordinary general meeting; Khimti Off the Ground- News release
    - Reports, etc.: K-03.01.01/0052 - K-03.01.01/0069, 1996 Oct- 2000 Nov (Box 92, Folder 7)
      Including regarding: Khimti news; HH meeting and letters regarding Khimti losses; Rock support design BPCH; Information leaflet; Civil Construction Progress status
    - "The Khimti Mirror" (magazine): K-03.01.01/0059, K-03.01.01/0060, 1998-1999 (Box 157, Folder 4)
    - Baseline survey draft and final report: K-03.01.01/0062, 1999 (Box 157, Folder 1)
    - "The Khimti Mirror" (magazine): K-03.01.01/63, 2000 (Box 165, Folder 4)
    - Correspondence, etc.: K-03.02.01 - RESTRICTED, 1995-1997 (Box 89, Folder 1)
  - Kathmandu University
    - Reports, etc.: K-04.01.01/0001 - K-04.01.01/0015, 1985 Aug- 1993 Jun (Box 91, Folder 9)
      Including regarding: Request for cooperation in a private campus; Outline for plans for Kathmandu Valley Campus and UMN funding package; Kathmandu University School of Education; Prospectus; UMN annual plan for 1
    - Reports, etc.: K-04.01.01/0016 - K-04.01.01/0035, 1993 Oct- 1996 Jun (Box 91, Folder 10)
      Including regarding: Establishment of a Total Technology M. Sc program at KU; Detailed annual report; Contractual agreement
    - Reports, etc.: K-04.01.01/0036 - K-04.01.01/0049, 1996 Jun 24- 1999 Oct (Box 92, Folder 1)
      Including regarding: KU: A Profile; UMN stipends; KU no longer private but independent; Annual and progress reports; KU Profile; Reports to UMN from KU; Requests for assistance from UMN; Letter of understanding between UMN and KU
    - Reports: General and KU Medical School: (K-04.01), 2003 (Box 210, Folder 2)
      See also KU School of Engineering, K-04.04.
    - Correspondence: K-04.02.01/0001 - RESTRICTED, 1994 (Box 89, Folder 5)
    - Correspondence: (K-04/02) - RESTRICTED, no date (Box 210, Folder 3)
    - KU / UMN Management Group minutes, including secondee reports: (K-04.03) - RESTRICTED, 2000-2006 (Box 210, Folder 4)
    - KU School of Engineering reports: (K-04.04), 1999-2007 (Box 210, Folder 5-6)
- L, Series XII
  - Lalitpur
    - District Clinics and Shanta Bhawan Community Health Program
      - Reports, etc.: L-01.01.01/0001 - L-01.01.01/0020, 1969 May- 1973 Nov (Box 92, Folder 8)
        Including regarding: Tour of District Clinics program; Referral of patients to SBH; Report on CHP; Shanta Bhawan outreach program; Food and nutrition survey of four areas
      - Reports, etc.: L-01.01.01/0021 - L-01.01.01/0045, 1974 Jan- 1976 Jun (Box 92, Folder 9)
        Including regarding: Nutrition report; Report on village compounder training; Revised description of CHP; Funding application; Proposal for Central Integration Committee for Integrated Basic Health Services
      - Reports, etc. - "The Symptom-Treatment Manual": L-01.01.01/0025/001, 1974 (Box 172, Folder 4)
      - Reports, etc.: L-01.01.01/0038 (Box 159, Folder 5)
      - Reports, etc.: L-01.01.01/0038 (Box 172, Folder 2)
      - Reports, etc.: L-01.01.01/0046 - L-01.01.01/0057, 1976 Sep- 1978 Aug (Box 92, Folder 10)
        Including regarding: Report to HSB; NRC reports; Small water supplies and water installation; Traditional birth attendants; List of teaching aides; Women health volunteers; MCH clinic evaluation
      - Reports, etc.: L-01.01.01/0058 - L-01.01.01/0087, 1978 Aug- 1981 Jun (Box 92, Folder 11)
        Including regarding: Notes for discussion on future of the program; Food shortage; Education booklets made available; Diagram of central level operation; Agriculture report; Agriculture supply centre
      - Reports, etc.: L-01.01.0/0072/001 (Box 158, Folder 3)
      - Reports, etc.: L-01.01.01/0088 - L-01.01.01/0099, 1981 Jul- 1982 Jan (Box 92, Folder 12)
        Including regarding: Report on CH workshop; Problems with village drinking water program; Report on tree planting program; Health section report; NFE and school proposals; Compilation of personnel and staff policies; Project split into two
    - Community Development Assistance Project
      - Reports, etc.: L-01.02.01/0001 - L-01.02.01/0016, 1981 May- 1983 Jan (Box 93, Folder 1)
        Including regarding: Diagram of CDAP relationships with UMN; Mother and child nutrition; Draft SOWR; PMC minutes; Grain storage proposal to FAO
      - Reports, etc.: L-01.02.01/0017 - L-01.02.01/0031, 1983 Jan 19- Dec (Box 93, Folder 2)
        Including regarding: PMC minutes; Detailed funding application; Central office location; RDC visit report; Tentative proposal regarding NRC structural change
      - Reports, etc.: L-01.02.01/0032 - L-01.02.01/0044, 1984 Jan- Oct (Box 93, Folder 3)
        Including regarding: PMC minutes; Tree planting proposal; Detailed reports; CDAP relationship survey; Baseline studies in Lalitpur: Identification income generating activities, Vols I-IV
      - Reports, etc.: L-01.02.01/0042 (Box 159, Folder 5)
      - Reports, etc.: L-01.02.01/0042 (Box 160, Folder 1)
      - Reports, etc.: L-01.02.01/0045 - L-01.02.01/0059, 1984 Nov- 1985 Jul (Box 93, Folder 4)
        Including regarding: Activities of CDAP; Relief for family whose house burned down; Rural Industries; PMC minutes; NFE visit report; For The Record: Evaluation of CDAP 1982-1985
      - Reports, etc.: L-01.02.01/0060 (Box 160, Folder 1)
    - Community Primary Health Care Project
      - Reports, etc.: L-01.03.01/0001 - L-01.03.01/0009, 1981 Mar- 1982 Jul (Box 93, Folder 5)
        Including regarding: Program proposal 1982-1986; Description of project and training activities; Volunteer's Seminar report; MCH course report; Proposed structure of relationship between UMN and HMG services
      - Reports, etc.: L-01.03.01/0010 - L-01.03.01/0024, 1983 Jan- Oct (Box 93, Folder 6)
        Including regarding: Report on clinics for 1982; Formation of HMG/UMN Health Coordination Committee; Lalitpur medical insurance plan and agreement; Structure of Lalitpur District Health Services; Funding application; Medical Insurance Scheme
      - Reports, etc.: L-01.03.01/0025 - L-01.03.01/0039, 1983 Oct- 1984 May (Box 93, Folder 7)
        Including regarding: Six months report on administration and volunteer program; Epidemic control incident; Suggestions for SOWR; PMC minutes; Seminar reports
      - Reports, etc.: L-01.03.01/0040 - L-01.03.01/0048, 1984 Jul-Oct (Box 93, Folder 8)
        Including regarding: Report on community financing medical insurance program; Six monthly report on roundworm control; PMC minutes; Primary health care
      - Reports, etc.: L-01.03.01/0049 - L-01.03.01/0054, 1984 Dec- 1985 Nov (Box 93, Folder 9)
        Including regarding: Morbidity assessment; Plans for training; Organisational structure; PMC minutes
      - Reports, etc.: L-01.04.01/001 - L-01.04.01/0007, 1983 Sep- 1985 Sep (Box 94, Folder 1)
        Including regarding: Establishment of CDHP officially authorized; CDHP functioning in practice; Description of CDHP in summary; Construction program
      - Reports,etc.: L-01.04.01/0006 (Box 160, Folder 2)
      - Reports, etc.: L-01.04.01/0008 - L-01.04.01/0022, 1985 Sep- 1986 Jan (Box 94, Folder 2)
        Including regarding: Community dental health program: summary; Staff report; PMC minutes; Two reports on NFE visits; Reports; Official announcement of formation of CDHP; Administration diagrams
      - Reports, etc.: L-01.04.01/0018 (Box 158, Folder 3)
      - Reports, etc.: L-01.04.01/0023 - L-01.04.01/0041, 1986 Jan- Jul (Box 94, Folder 3)
        Including regarding: Field administration proposal; Phasing out components of CDHP; Forestry and horticulture meeting; PMC minutes; Report on nutrition visit to Malta; Outline of health care survey to be done
      - Reports, etc. - "Community Potable Water": L-01.04.01/0038 (Box 172, Folder 3)
      - Reports, etc.: L-01.04.01/0042 - L-01.04.01/0057, 1986 Aug- 1987 Feb (Box 94, Folder 4)
        Including regarding: Meeting regarding forestry; Parameters and general direction of CDHP; RDC visit and detailed report; Independent clinics in Lalitpur; Development section activities proposal
      - Reports, etc.: L-01.04.01/0058 - L-01.04.01/0072, 1987 Feb- 1987 Sep (Box 94, Folder 5)
        Including regarding: Health Post construction: lessons learned; PMC minutes; Comparative statistics; RDC trip report; Circular on child survival; Forestry and horticulture work; Medical insurance scheme
      - Reports, etc.: L-01.04.02/001 - L-01.04.02/0011, 1987 Sep- 1988 Jan (Box 94, Folder 6)
        Including regarding: PMC minutes and SOWR; Conditions if CDHP were to act as DPHO, notes on discussion; CDHP leaflet; Structure of CDHP to rest of UMN; NFE seminar
      - Reports, etc.: L-01.04.02/012 - L-01.04.02/0023, 1988 Mar- Nov (Box 94, Folder 7)
        Including regarding: NFE Seminar; Report of RDC visit; Application to ICCO; Development section workshop; PMC minutes; Statement of direction for CDHP; Trip report and project proposal
      - Reports, etc.: L-01.04.02/024 - L-01.04.02/0034, 1989 Jan- Jul (Box 94, Folder 8)
        Including regarding: Problems in supporting field staff; RDC visit report in detail; PMC minutes; Using agriculture in CDHP; Patients referred to Patan Hospital; Newsletter of CDHP Day; Detailed annual report
      - Reports, etc.: L-01.04.02/035 - L-01.04.02/0044, 1989 Aug- 1990 Jan (Box 95, Folder 1)
        Including regarding: Change towards the poor; PMC minutes; History of project for UMN 35th booklet; Medical insurance coverage statistics; Field report on rural development program
      - Reports, etc.: L-01.04.02/045 - L-01.04.02/0054, 1990 Feb- Mar (Box 95, Folder 2)
        Including regarding: In service training plans; PMC minutes; Statement of Direction and Working Rules; WSC (water supplies) trip report; ICCO reports, English and Dutch
      - Reports, etc.: L-01.04.03/0000 - L-01.04.03/0010, 1990 Apr- Jul (Box 95, Folder 3)
        Including regarding: Today's demand in the health section; Correspondence and papers on management; Management improvement strategy; CDHP working rules discussion and decision
      - Reports, etc.: L-01.04.03/011 - L-01.04.03/0020, 1990 Jul- Dec (Box 95, Folder 4)
        Including regarding: Detailed annual reports; Development section workshop report; EAC (PMC) minutes; Descriptive agreement with ICCO; Proposal for community development in Malta
      - Reports, etc.: L-01.04.03/021 - L-01.04.03/0028, 1990-1991 Jan (Box 95, Folder 5)
        Including regarding: Research proposition; Proposal for participants' consideration; Proposal and notes for discussion; Management: summary of discussion
      - Reports, etc.: L-01.04.03/0021, 1990 (Box 172, Folder 2)
      - Reports, etc.: L-01.04.03/029 - L-01.04.03/0043, 1991 Feb- Aug (Box 95, Folder 6)
        Including regarding: CDHP management review; PH-CDHP Functional Coordinating Committee; Detailed annual plans; Introduction fo NFE in CDHP; Women farmers in S. Lalitpur; Report on development section workshop
      - Reports, etc.: L-01.04.03/044 - L-01.04.03/0056, 1991 Aug- 1992 Feb (Box 95, Folder 7)
        Including regarding: Introduction to Agriculture Component; EAC (PMC) minutes; Project director's duties; Report on "Priorities" questionnaire; Guidelines for urgent and very high risk obstetric referral; Comments on CDHP; Annual reports
      - Reports, etc.: L-01.04.03/0050 (Box 158, Folder 3)
      - Reports, etc.: L-01.04.03/0051 (Box 160, Folder 2)
      - Reports, etc. - Follow-up report: L-01.04.03/0055, 1991 (Box 172, Folder 2)
      - Reports, etc.: L-01.04.03/057 - L-01.04.03/0069, 1992 Feb- Dec (Box 95, Folder 8)
        Including regarding: Evaluation workshop: minutes and paper on strategic planning; EAC (PMC) minutes; CDHP vision and statement; Brief annual report; Newsletters; Measles outbreak in 1990
      - Reports, etc.: L-01.04.04/0001 - L-01.04.04/0010, 1993 Jan- Apr (Box 95, Folder 9)
        Including regarding: Report of measles outbreak in Lalitpur, 1990; Proposal for grants; New strategies for MCH; A visit to South Lalitpur; EAC (PMC) minutes
      - Reports, etc.: L-01.04.04/0002 (Box 159, Folder 3)
      - Reports, etc.: L-01.04.04/0011 - L-01.04.04/0024, 1993 May- 1994 (Box 95, Folder 10)
        Including regarding: Newsletters; Impact evaluation feedback meeting; Maternal mortality; Safe motherhood; Impact observations by early UMNers on revisits; Thesis on discontinuing refresher training and supervision of traditional birth attendants
      - Reports, etc.: L-01.04.04/0023 (Box 160, Folder 4)
      - Reports, etc.: L-01.04.04/0025 - L-01.04.04/0034, 1994 Apr- Nov (Box 96, Folder 1)
        Including regarding: Community Dentistry in Lalitpur; Summary annual report; Final report to Swedish NGOs; EAC minutes; Newsletters; Information sent to donors
      - Reports, etc.: L-01.04.04/0035 - L-01.04.04/0037, 1994 Oct- 1995 Feb (Box 96, Folder 2)
        Including regarding: Newsletter; Summary and detailed annual plans 1995/96; EAC minutes and presentation on Annual plan to EAC
      - Reports, etc.: L-01.04.04/0038 - L-01.04.04/0047, 1995 Feb- Nov (Box 96, Folder 3)
        Including regarding: Child Health Care in CDHP; HP Committee Workshop Report; Newsletter (Nepali); CDHP working rules; Using community methods and skills; Transfer of staff to HMG
      - Reports,etc.: L-01.04.04/0041/001 (Box 160, Folder 4)
      - Reports, etc. re. Well program: L-01.04.04/0048, 1995 (Box 172, Folder 4)
      - Reports, etc.: L-01.04.05/0000 - L-01.04.05/0005, 1995 Aug-1996 Mar (Box 96, Folder 4)
        Including regarding: Summary detailed annual reports; Draft strategic plan to 200 ft.; Extended AC (PMC) minutes; Review of Five Year Plan, 1990-95
      - Reports, etc.: L-01.04.05/0006 - L-01.04.05/0009, 1996 Feb- Sep (Box 96, Folder 5)
        Including regarding: Papers on Mahwanpur: Program A. Three Months' Action Plan and K.M. Shakya letter; Summary and detailed annual reports; Report of forestry visit
      - Reports, etc.: L-01.04.05/0010 - L-01.04.05/0016, 1996 Sep- 1997 (Box 96, Folder 6)
        Including regarding: Funding appeal; PMC meeting; Long Term Plans
      - Reports, etc.: L-01.04.05/0017 - L-01.04.05/0018, 1997 Mar (Box 96, Folder 7)
        Including regarding: Summary and detailed annual plans; Funding request; Detailed letter to ICCO
      - Reports, etc.: L-01.04.05/0019 - L-01.04.05/0025, 1997 Mar- Oct (Box 96, Folder 8)
        Including regarding: Summary and detailed annual plans; Geographical and functional areas of work: Brief description; Integrated rainy season workshop report; Lalitpur medical insurance schedule: A status report after 20 years
      - Reports, etc.: L-01.04.05/0020 (Box 160, Folder 2)
      - Reports, etc.: L-01.04.06/0001 - L-01.04.06/0007, 1998 Jan- 1998 Feb (Box 97, Folder 1)
        Including regarding: Leaflet; Funding proposal; Annual plans for 1998/99: Summary and detailed; Makwanpur Field visit report
      - Reports, etc.: L-01.04.06/0008 - L-01.04.06/0010, 1998 May-Aug (Box 97, Folder 2)
        Including regarding: Funding proposal; Oral Health, Lalitpur, Health post target area; Follow up of agriculture centre buildings, Women's Cooperative Groups and Ashrang Cooperative Mill
      - Reports, etc.: L-01.04.06/0011 - L-01.04.06/0018, 1998 Sep- 1999 May (Box 97, Folder 3)
        Including regarding: Overview report 1998; Family magazine; Funding application and response, ICCO; Summary and detailed plans; PMC; Betini impact evaluation
      - Reports, etc. Mental health survey in South Lalitpur: L-01.04.06/18/001, 1999 (Box 165, Folder 4)
      - Reports, etc.: L-01.04.06/0019 - L-01.04.06/0022, 1999 Jul- 2000 Jan (Box 97, Folder 4)
        Including regarding: Recommendations for the betterment of Makwanpur program; Summary and detailed Annual Reports; Six month report to January 2000
      - Management study (Afful): (L-01.04), 1991 (Box 210, Folder 7)
      - Reports, plans, etc. (L-01.04), 1991-2004 (Box 211, Folder 1-2)
    - Urban Primary Health Care Program/ YALA Urban Health Program